sweetclipart.com 2018-08-18

# Privacy Policy - Free Clip Art

**Privacy Policy for** [Sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/)

_Specifics added for the GDPR law: [Updated May 2018] I use Google Analytics and Google Adsense on sweetclipart.com and m.sweetclipart.com, and a very limited version of Statcounter. My Google Analytics stats are retained for 14 months then are overwritten. My Statcounter stats are usually retained for about 1-2 days then are overwritten. Anonymous stats are also logged by my hosting account, Hostgator; I keep those logs for up to 1 year. I only use these stats for personal use, such as to analyze keyword trends, traffic, and backlinks, and to prevent abuse of my website (for example, to block bot IP addresses). These stats are mostly anonymous.  _ _I do not collect information that personally identifies any of my visitors, and I do not share my statistics logs with anyone._

If you require any more information or have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free to contact me at [sweetclipart.com/contact](http://sweetclipart.com/contact).

At [sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/), the privacy of my visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/) and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[Sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/) does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/).  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to [sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/) and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of my advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on my site. My advertising partners include: Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[Sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [Sweetclipart.com](http://sweetclipart.com/)'s privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
